[dramatic music playing]
[man] Ben! Ethan! Wake up. ya goldbricks!
I got donuts!
Homemade?
Why would they be homemade?
Who makes donuts at home?
-[suspenseful music playing]
-[whoosh]
[whooshing continues]
[loud banging]
What in the hell?
[mechanical voice]
Triad Industries is under attack.
You are not the targets.
For your own safety. get out. now.
[grunts]
[panting and groaning]
[suspenseful music playing]
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
[whooshing]
[theme music playing]
[dramatic music playing]
[Pennyworth]
Now. that is the definition of a rum do.
At least there were no casualties.
That’s something.
One wonders what was inside
that might cause such an explosion.
The Express says "electrical fire."
Confined to three of the uppermost floors?
In a building containing
no industrial equipment?
Don’t you find that odd?
What's odd is either of you
caring about this at all.
If the papers are saying
it’s an accident.
GCPD must’ve signed off.
I don't know.
There are an awful lot
of unanswered questions.
Why are you here on a Saturday. Lucius?
Do you ever stop working?
Today is Monday. and that means...
paperwork.
Monday? Really?
Triad Industries?
Do I know that name?
The CEOs approached
your company for funding. Rejected.
I remember.
They gave some kind of presentation.
A new power source?
Ultrium.
They had documents and a pitch reel.
All still at my office.
Great. Bring everything along tomorrow.
We’ll screen it in the theater.
Pennyworth can make popcorn!
And why am I doing this?
What? I'm taking an active hand.
[dramatic music playing]
Pennyworth. I'm inside.
I hear you. sir.
My notepad is at the ready.
The Express undersold it.
No way an electrical fire caused this.
These look like...
blast craters.
They appear to be
from simultaneous explosions.
[Pennyworth. over device]
As in grenades or bombs?
Inconclusive. I need to look at--
You've done a good job
keeping a lid on things. Sal.
Thanks. Mr. Hardwick. sir.
But I was thinkin' maybe we let
the cops in on what's been happening?
Let the partners decide
what we can handle.
You just keep doing
what you've been doing.
Keeping a lid on things.
What is that?
-[suspenseful music playing]
-[both gasp]
[grunting]
[groaning]
[grunts]
[dramatic music playing]
-[projector whirring]
-[classical music playing]
[woman] All over the world.
people are starving.
Epidemics kill millions across the globe.
Nations wage war over territory
and resources.
Generation after generation.
century after century.
Is humanity fated to repeat
these horrors forever?
I say. “no.”
Not if we look up.
Our future is in the stars.
Exploration.
Invention.
This future is made possible by
my new rocket-based technology.
and by Ultrium. the fuel of the future.
Clean. pure. inexhaustible.
The perfect power for a golden destiny.
It’s time for humanity to blast off!
Why did we pass on this again?
Misters Lydecker. Lawford. and Hardwick
wouldn’t let us
independently evaluate Ultrium and
the designs for their rocket technology.
Am I sensing a change of mind on Triad?
Let's just say. my interest is peaked.
You wanna take another look
at this project?
See how far along they are?
I do.
I like this version of you. Bruce.
Participation suits you.
I’ll set up a meeting.
I don't know why I set up this meeting.
You never come to meetings.
You have no idea how things
are supposed to go.
Don’t worry. I went to the same school
as you. remember?
[man] Gentlemen!
Warren Lawford. CEO of Triad Industries.
Good to see you again.
And this is Bruce Wayne.
Of course it is. A pure pleasure. sir.
We've got so much to show you.
Thank you for taking this meeting
on such short notice.
Nonsense.
We welcome your renewed interest.
-You gave us the high hat last time.
-Hardwick. is it?
It’s Lucius’s job to zealously
protect my assets.
And I do.
But I couldn’t get your Ultrium project
out of my mind.
I know exactly what you mean. Mr. Wayne.
Ultrium is a miracle element.
Nearly unlimited power generated
by even the tiniest amounts.
Amazing.
Honestly. I was hoping to meet with
Dr. Sutton. Her designs are incredible.
A genius like our Roxy comes along
once in a generation. [chuckles]
The world will sing her praises
for centuries to come. but--
Sutton's dead.
[man] Lucius Fox.
Hello. again. Long time.
Armand Lydecker. meet Bruce Wayne.
We’re giving Ultrium another look.
So Warren said.
So... Dr. Sutton?
Oh. you're talking about Roxy.
You see. there was... an accident.
An explosion at her home lab.
Tragic. Killed instantly. the poor girl.
Nothing left of her at all.
[tense music playing]
[Lydecker] The important thing
is most of Roxy’s notes.
her designs were copied
prior to her death.
Enough to make sure her legacy survives.
We’ll use it to usher in a new golden age.
That’s... commendable.
[Bruce] This prototype really
is impressive.
The project's in its final phase?
Even without Dr. Sutton?
Losing Roxy was a blow.
But yes. we’re actually ahead of schedule.
We’re demonstrating our working
rocket prototype this weekend.
Think of it. A projectile as big
as an office building.
powered by a single brick of Ultrium!
We’d love for you to attend
our little demo.
Just us. a few foreign dignitaries.
-and people with money and vision.
-[dramatic music playing]
We're taking no chances.
The Ultrium will travel by rail to be
stored at a secure Triad testing site.
[Lawford] Nothing will stop the launch.
A squad of Gunther’s best men will be
on guard the whole time.
[dramatic music continues]
[train horn blaring]
[rocket whooshing]
[suspenseful music playing]
[horn blaring continues]
A lot of fuss for a shiny brick. huh?
What the hell?
[loud banging]
[suspenseful music continues]
[grunting]
[grunts]
Another one!
[grunting]
[groans]
[grunts and groans]
[yells]
[grunting]
[groans]
[grunts]
[Batman] Dr. Sutton?
[suit whirring]
[groans]
[grunts]
[tense music playing]
[tense music continues]
[tires squealing]
[tires screeching]
[rocket whooshing in distance]
[dramatic music playing]
[Batman] I saw her. Pennyworth.
Four Triad locations destroyed
in the last year.
[Pennyworth]
And not the result of accidents.
One? Accident.
Two? Coincidence.
Three. four. five now with the train.
There’s a six month gap between
the destruction at Dr. Sutton’s home lab
and the first--
Are we calling them attacks officially?
Followed by the machine warehouse.
Now. this recent attack on the train.
and at the Triad home office.
[Batman] Only their records library
was destroyed.
Patents. blueprints. formulas.
You believe Dr. Sutton
is responsible for all of it.
[Batman] This was caused
by small explosions.
the kind made
by that rocket pistol of hers.
She's using her inventions
to damage Triad.
Curious.
Why go to these lengths?
Why fake her own death?
Too many questions.
But I've got an idea
where to get some answers.
[dramatic music playing]
[doors creak open]
[tense music playing]
[creaking]
[doors scrape open]
[dramatic music playing]
[Batman] You have to stop this.
Dr. Sutton.
[Sutton] You shouldn't have come here.
You haven’t killed anyone yet.
But your luck will run out.
This vendetta can’t go on--
[Sutton] The masked vigilante
is lecturing me about vendettas?
-[suspenseful music playing]
-[Sutton groans]
[grunts]
You need help.
The accident obviously hurt your mind.
Accident? It was them.
I found out what those animals
were doing with my work!
You’re trying to sell my plans
to foreign powers!
Dr. Sutton. Roxy...
be reasonable.
Rockets to the stars cost money.
This is how we--
You've breached our contract!
You'll be hearing from my lawyer.
[dramatic music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
[gasps]
[dramatic music playing]
When I discovered their plans for my work.
they tried to remove me.
If that’s true. they’re criminals.
I can get to the bottom of it.
Bring them to justice.
Where were you when they were
corrupting my work?
Where were you when they tried to kill me?
[Batman groans]
[suspenseful music playing]
[groans]
[dramatic music playing]
-[Batman] Sutton's obsessed. Pennyworth.
-And so I gather. sir.
Her campaign seems to have been
quite successful thus far.
This testing facility
is the last place left.
She'll certainly attack it then.
The demonstration is tomorrow.
There’ll be guests. company personnel.
In situations like this.
many would call in the police.
Perhaps warn Commissioner Gordon
of the impending--
Gordon's people can't handle her.
With her technology.
she'd cut through them like butter.
Then it's down to you...
again.
But the testing ground
is hundreds of miles from Gotham.
However will you get there in time?
[dramatic music playing]
[Lawford] The rocket is a magnificent
example of Triad technology.
but the real miracle is the power source.
Ultrium is clean. reusable.
and easy to produce.
That behemoth is powered by a cube
no bigger than a paperweight.
Welcome to the future.
ladies and gentleman.
It’s one you will own.
At wholesale prices.
[clapping]
[dramatic music playing]
At least try to grow a spine. Armand.
Don't you get it?
What’s in the rocket is our last cube
of Ultrium. If the test fails--
Your whining is starting
to get on my nerves!
-Stop it. Both of you.
-Let’s call it off. Warren.
We can say
there were technical difficulties.
Call them all back in a few months.
“Call them all back?”
They won’t come!
This is our only chance!
All our assets are tied
to today’s success.
Once they see what we have.
we’ll be awash in government contracts.
Private investment. Trust me.
Roxy's still out there!
Relax. Even if she does show. this time
my boys are ready for anything she’s got.
See? Everything’s going to plan.
Right.
Start the countdown!
[beeps]
[suspenseful music playing]
[suspenseful music continues]
[grunts]
[grunting and groaning]
[groans]
[grunts]
It's over. Dr. Sutton.
Look around! [grunts]
Don't you see where we are?
[dramatic music playing]
This is my work.
Mine!
They’re selling it to madmen!
Mass murderers.
They’ll turn the whole world
into a perpetual war z--
[gunfire]
[suspenseful music playing]
It’s called "business." Roxy.
Kill them! Kill them both!
[groaning]
Why couldn't you just take the money?
Let the men handle the business.
I won't have that blood on my hands!
[grunts]
You see now?
I’ve destroyed everything
they stole from me.
All but one piece of Ultrium!
The one in the rocket.
I can rewire it. make sure the test fails.
It’ll bankrupt Triad.
[suspenseful music continues]
[gun clicks]
That's it. I'm out of ammo.
I'm not.
Warren! Launch the rocket!
[Hardwick. over intercom]
Do you hear me? Launch!
-Warren...
-Launch the rocket!
Sir? We’re only halfway
through the countdown.
-I said. "Launch." Now!
-[whimpers]
[dramatic music playing]
I'll deal with them. Go!
-[suspenseful music playing]
-[grunting and groaning]
[grunts and groans]
[frustrated grunts]
[groans and grunts]
[groans]
[grunting]
[suspenseful music continues]
[groans]
[grunts and groans continue]
[suspenseful music continues]
[chuckling]
Too late. freak!
There's nothing she can do.
The demo will be a complete success!
-[suspenseful music playing]
-[struggling. groaning]
[dramatic music playing]
[gasping]
[pained groaning]
[dramatic music playing]
-Are you quite sure about this. sir?
-It's what she wanted.
In the right hands.
Dr. Sutton's work could be transformative.
And whose hands would that be?
[emotional music playing]
[ominous music playing]
[man whistling tune]
[whistling continues]
[scary music playing]
[credits music playing]
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org